Guide to the New York State College of Human Ecology Admissions Office records, 1925-2017.
New York State College of Human Ecology Admissions Office records, 1925-2017.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State College of Human Ecology Admissions Office records, 1925-2017.
23-11-2928
New York State College of Human Ecology. Admissions Office.
1.5 cubic ft.
Correspondence, memoranda, studies, profiles, statistics, publications, reports, and other records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, memoranda, studies, profiles, statistics, publications, reports, and other records of the office.
Includes orientation t-shirts.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, memoranda, studies, profiles, statistics, publications, reports, and other records of the office.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Human Ecology. Admissions Office.; Cornell University--Administration.; New York State College of Home Economics.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIAL
See also collection #23-2-2817, New York State College of Human Ecology records, Boxes 107-109 contain admissions brochures
CONTAINER LIST
- Early correspondence and memoranda, 1925, 1932, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Study on admissions responsibility and criteria, pre-1967-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Admissions profile, 1966, 1969, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Recommended program of study for bachelor's candidates preparing for international home economics assignments, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Admissions report, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Reports on undergraduates, 1974-1975, 1976-1977, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Admissions reports and highlights, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Admissions annual reports, 1960, 1981-1982, 1982-1983, 1983-1984, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Three year enrollment plan, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Ten Years in Admissions, 1977-1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Ten Years in Student Services, 1978-1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Statistical and other admissions reports, 1968-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Statistical reports, 1973-1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Twelve year comparison of freshmen admissions statistics, 1978-1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Minority statistics, 1978-1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Profiles of classes, 1984-1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Student services annual report, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Admissions annual report, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Admissions annual report, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Student services annual report, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Student services annual report, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Student services annual report, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Undergraduate affairs annual report, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Degrees conferred, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Registration statistics, 1932-1962 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Application for admissions and program for freshman orientation, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Resident Educational Policies Committee - In Absentia Study, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Sub-committee on secondary education curriculum annual reports, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Summer jobs of undergraduates, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Reports on graduates of the class of 1965 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Committee on Undergraduate Education, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Admissions statistics, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Admissions Policy Committee, 1976-1980-03 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Admissions Policy Committee, 1980-04-1981-08 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Admissions Policy Committee, 1981-09-1982-05 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Admissions Policy Committee minutes, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Admissions annual report, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Admissions plans, 1984-1985, 1988-1989, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Update from admissions, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Admissions facts, 1989, 2006, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Admissions office correspondence, memos, activities, programs, 1989-1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Post-graduate placement data, highlights of the class of 1993 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Admission Student and Career Services overview, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Models for orking with undergraduates in research, 2002-01 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Profile of the class of 2000 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Profile of the class of 2003 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Undergraduate Affairs "Who We Are", 2004 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Ambassadors training manual, 2007-03 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Transfer day packet, 2007-11 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Studies, surveys done concerning the closing of the north wing in MVR Hall, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Sample admissions questionnaire, Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Brief college histories, Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Publication "Hotline", 1981-1996 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Publication "The Interchange", 1986-03, 1986-04, 1994-09 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Admissions publications, brochures, 1980-2000 (Box 1, Folder 42-43)
- Human Ecology admissons teleconference, Undated; V-11602-11603 (Box 1)
- Human Ecology Update, 1998-08-27; V-11604 (Box 1)
  8mm video cassette
- Oreintation t-shirts, 2000-2017; MU-2722-2732 (Box 2)
- Student advising team mug, Undated; MU-2764 (Box 2)